# **Emma Woods**

## **Summary**

Highly experienced project management professional with extensive experience in online digital media environments. Core competencies include project management, business development, strategic product direction, client and vendor relationship management. Graduate student of the MS Applied Data Science program at Syracuse University, with experience in statistics and analysis, data mining and predictive machine learning technologies.

### **Education**

MS Applied Data Science, Syracuse University

September 2020

BSc Information Studies, University of North London

June 1997

### **Professional Certifications**

Project Management Professional (PMP)

January 2019

Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer (MCSE)

**April 1999** 

# **Work Experience**

#### Director of Advertising Operations, SuperMarket Television

Feb 2019 - Feb 2020

- Directed Ad Server Operations for digital network located in 100+ grocery stores
- Managed Sys Admin and backend operations for proprietary video advertising delivery platform
- Responsible for supporting advertising agency partners in the distribution of digital assets across the network

#### Director of Affiliate Relations, The Convenience Network

Aug 2013 - Feb 2019

- Directed technical team responsible for maintaining and developing proprietary Digital Out of Home ad delivery platform, developed in Ruby and utilizing app server and cloud storage systems (Heroku/AWS)
- Project Manager responsible for installation of 350 client sites within convenience store ad delivery network
- Direct client support for c-store network of 500+ retail sites

#### VP Sales Operations, Voices Heard Media, Inc.

Sept 2010 - Aug 2013

- Provided customer relationship and data analytics for clients of web-based user engagement platform
- Directed Account Management team in providing sales support and technical training program